<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Tails-MVT</title>
    <link>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Tails-MVT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Tails-MVT</title>
      <link>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Tails-MVT Tails-MVT is a customised version of Tails that has the Mobile Verification Toolkit preinstalled and working out of the box. Tails-MVT is meant for non-advanced users. If you have a technical background, you may want to setup MVT yourself and follow the official MVT Documentation.
Experiencing an issue? If you are experiencing problems with Tails-MVT, please raise an issue on our Github repository page.
Contact To get in contact with us, write us at contact@tails-mvt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyse Android devices</title>
      <link>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/analyse-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/analyse-android/</guid>
      <description>Analyse Android devices  1.1 Preparing the Android device To analyse an Android device, the developer options and USB debugging need to be enabled. On the device, head to the Settings -&amp;gt; About phone and press the build number several times. Once the developer options are enabled, enable USB Debugging from within Settings -&amp;gt; System -&amp;gt; Developer options and toggle USB debugging.
1.2 Perform analysis To analyse your device, connect it to the laptop with a compatible cable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyse iOS devices</title>
      <link>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/analyse-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/analyse-ios/</guid>
      <description>Analyse iOS devices  1.1 Preparing folders To analyse an iOS device, create a folder structure according to the one listed below. It can be done through the File Explorer found under Applications -&amp;gt; Accessories -&amp;gt; Files or by opening a terminal and typing mkdir -p ios/backup ios/backup-decrypted ios/result.
To open a terminal, press the Windows or Super button on the keyboard and search for terminal or select it from Applications -&amp;gt; Utilities -&amp;gt; Terminal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started</title>
      <link>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tails-mvt.github.io/page/get-started/</guid>
      <description>Get Started To use Tails-MVT, download the latest release under releases or build the image from source. To build Tails-MVT from source, see Building a Tails image.
1.1 Creating an installation media After obtaining the image, flash it to a USB drive or SD card in order to create a bootable media. To do so we recommend using balenaEtcher. If flashing from Linux, you can use balenaEtcher, gnome-disk-utility or dd as described in Install Tails from Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
